Ok,...thank you very much.
...this light and I must be exhausted after the conference a and between to get the
...so hopeless and content...keywords types the next out before...some
jones on the api architect one item microsoft and ism until about today.
So, you could...to the nation will...and twenty fifty.
And, then do tour through the basis of our api...new features we've released recently and
released today and then go into the main demos around how to
pull that together to do stuff with one that number three sixty five
and then come back to talking about a roadmap...what's next so twenty fifty?
One digital note-taking from microsoft completely cross platform and
free on every platform is are coming universal
...application is archive application you can see video
...the key things about one night and I real differentiator for us is
...content is extremely rich and particularly strictly
free extremely free-fall.
...many which content...pictures aac imbedded spreadsheets.
Lists and how point is that it doesn't constrain you is your in the early form of working on your ideas
...working on projection just put anything down where if you likeand,
really just find a way that works...we'll see that has some impacts
...on impacts in api design how...api is...
Source the business opportunity...here with one that well.
What really is ubiquitous now as well as being
cross platform on every device from laptops down
through tablets and phones to new wearable apps on the apple
watch android where we also pre installed in a huge number of
places you can guarantee that you're...already have the app
pre installed on every new windows machine with our universe...we...on the some galaxy
fsix and...six edge and a bunch of...android tablets?
From a variety of manufactures.
Tens of millions of
...uses in...and then when you connectors up three...ecosystem and api is to offer three
sixty-five api...access to the hundreds of millions of general issues so we've been around as
...api from abigail want itself has been around for method
genius we lost our api little over a year-ago much last year we focus at the time on
...consumer api people logging image microsoft identity we've already developed a
broad ecosystem based on that a whole lot about...gallery can...down the bottom get
...and,hundreds of apps registered against our input
couple first polity...pick and a note office...a pockets
...more that later...clipper can...things of the web
...extension or bookmark look for the roswell...favor browsers?
Grab web content...just exactly how you like...capturing grab...digital memory still.
So, if you've.
Seen the office three sixty five vision in the keynote for developers or any of the other...three sixty
...sessions you...we think about this is a
to prong thing we think about extending the user experience.
And, we think about accessing the underlying data so
...the user experience to get reach all of those uses...hundreds of millions of users
who have office and then integrating all of that back-end data your own data amount
data so the one I to api is really focus on data
...the moment I'm going to talk about the rest api primarily today
...show you how we think about that when integrated with the rest of office to go and get that reach to
uses and how you can couple...into the ecosystem and, hook up to all of those
...as well bringing one-line data in your own data as well?
So, obviously from the talk the talk is a bit of...really
we're announcing today support in the one that api for office three sixty five and...say we for a year we've
now been working on a consumer api...today we have pretty close to parity
withoutin preview today office three sixty five.
Couple of...which I'll show at the end that we're still...wrinkles out of so what are the scenarios one of the first
things you do with...through the api typically the first thing
usually do is to go and take some content unlit up and send it off to
...so maybe there's a reporting your application or maybe or upgrades diagrams of some kind anyone
...insert those into one...take the customers information
of created in your app go push into all night so it's there is part of the...memory store
...can reuse it...projects so one that's content language is html.
Very simply don't have to...learn some new pagedescription language to build a program one
...html skills you've got just work...to sub-set of html five
...pretty much the obvious things if you can see it in the one...you why and imagine what the html
...you would...lattice then we'll probably support it...pretty good way to describe it you just
...this is about the most simple page you could postand,
just say hey his body within this cases...and,
his picture capped place kittens and awesome way to go get
...pictures of the web by the way any size you need.
So, that's great but what I said...just create a simple page within...picture under the
Very flat but free-form content is really what...all...moment.
So, again, create free-form content you get them to absolutely position things on the page...be a bit more creative
...you put things.
To do that we're just going to use standard
csi styling inline in the html you can see here.
The understanding of the positions and, using absolute positions on the
dave positive that I'm now going to put in some text and then.
Yet another capture positioned over on the right.
So, here's a cat person.
And, nobody here's a dog person...you guys again have a really bad time...this presentation.
...I'm very sorry.
...not for the presentation for-you being...people.
So,...go ...the looking all this in...go and look at and some code
...so I'm just going to flip over great way to kick the
...are api is we've got a api
...from our friends over apathy.
In get to this...to adapt
...dot com and just give you a way to gump ugly api and just make some
calls and experiment around this case...connected to our consumer service so I'm going to go and,
choose to...page and...
Okay.
It's not terribly big online resolution automate little bit bigger.
...existing content a little bit.
Oops now I can't say.
Science...out content whoops.
...to the bottom a little...trying to play with two scold balls at once so bear with me
...say...an.
Shipment.
Back to top again.
Ok.
now we can go...the content unless we're just going to...the contin indirectly.
...my powerpoint...really...a coding to...tell you otherwise.
Argonne post...
And,...with my absolute positions...image with
...positions and go-go send-off...that service
...and loop minus one authors run out...radially...
No, it isn't incorrect appreciate.
...more drawing which...
...hubcaps local.
The question is did that post-it.
And, it's going back to the original...and, we go all right so send-off.
...that ok so that's created the page so you can see that is just send-me the
response back here and I've got the usual kind of response I get from
...go-to json packet tell me what was just created the typical properties hear about the page
...title of the page when it was created to last modified it all the sort of
engine normally expect to get a couple of really interesting properties.
Down...into this links object got a couple of urls to be able to go
and launch that page either in the web client for one note or...like.
...the rich client link.
Ccs a one not...url I'm going to grab that and this post into the browser.
And, that's going to launch my...to application which of...to...
Here we...it's launch may and create mode...patient when consular of going.
That's creating a page and it's going to look into the next sourcing you today so
...only them when I want to enrich my experience...picket to say...to the user where you want
...put this page within a one that we have a hierarchical structure of notebooks with
sections within them the pages within those and then we also have a
...section...if you need to deep a hierarchy section groups or recursive containment structure that we
can have if you really want that kind of...more complex notebook so to do that I'm going to
...one of sm collapse.
This sample that we just put a new version of this upon get up today...switch over to.
...about so, this upon get how did I just I three sixty five support for
...api explore application is relatives you can see what it does
so this essentially gives you ways to post a whole bunch of different request to
our api surface and play...results and see what you get back
...conflict between over three sixty five authentication or consumer authentication...can have a look
at driving those sections first thing we do is say we'll take a list of all my books.
So, I'm going to guarantee both this.
Just...into the code assuming...I'll...of...I'm going to create
and http request as you expect...code on-going...authentication so we using
...to authentication...the rest about...three sixty five services I'm going to set
...a baritone could and that's going to go login so.
And,...is going to ensure...of scopes...set of scopes...talking choose on the api
...tell you what your app is allowed to do...through oath
...I can do to the one night...encouraged to do is go...the smallest
scope the you need to get the job dub uses...take confidence from the fact
that only want to...to page...application or you want to do is be able to edit the pages that you
are the created one of enhance you can see the moines us for every scope please do bob
what users will typically freak out when they say some huge list of demands for your application...against need to.
...that most...
And, I'll from the code.
And, you can see that here I'm just calling the get method my api route.
Is one I dot com baiter api...notes which is a...path froze and then I'm going to goal and
...can't get all of...that run...
And, it's going to come back and bring me that the body the and...latin...be easier to see
it's not too easy to see...online jason parser here...I was going to cost in...
...copyright...
So, I can say we just...structure based on for network and again it's the kind of indeed...to see
...notebook in...book shared with anybody the...the
...last modified time...sort of thing again the...urls let me go and open
up particular notebook in either of the one that clients and features the one client you so
...open the windows desktop...you can use that same url on any device...go and
open the appropriate client on the divisor installed in so...just what's cross platform seamlessly.
So, that's my notebook what about...to drill down we've got
a hierarchical structure for looking here I've got urls to let me go
and use...media to go and jump through to see the sections in the notebook of section url the
...group url that's a lot of round-trip you can...the session url if I
...sections of an see the pages and I can just keep going through great for exploring the api
not-so-great for performance so because...using...data we can go...botha and
use something called expand so...no data allows you to walk across relationships
...data model in our case walk across the hari of hierarchy of wug and go and get everything in
one go.
So, go back and see...
This chalmers going to run that thrill invalid debugging it and we'll see what we've got.
...it's the same not book but now I'm going to scroll down when I get to the...see
...imbedded all of the session requests and...similar...just listed out...children of...book
...single round-trip and...got the pages url...could have done the expand further down and
drilled into the pages got muscle list of pages factors complicated expression which...find in the
slides...get the whole thing a complete are rocky of everything in
your notebook all the way down from the network through the section groups even if they
...all the way into the pages so you can do a whole lot in one rancher...be...like.
Ok, so, pages that's the next interesting thing to look at.
So, if I can...section.
Because again because...a query language for pages of
this completely standard across all of a three sixty five inputs so we can go and say hey go and
...the pages where the title contains paris all the pages created after a
certain time so here I'm going to...use a title query and.
If I go and look...and see what pages I've got to query full and flipped my business
...three sixty five I've got a bunch pages obviously...there's actually
...those not random chat software to get special permission to...
...got a bunch of pages that have page in the title so, let's go and see if we can pull those back.
Page in that.
The some of the debug.
...through and you can see the message so here we're just using the same types of data provides
let's do the query so we...the pages endpoint.
...saying and filter equals contains and then title in the string...images page
...contains
...page in the title property of any of my page objects...from that.
You should see that I've got a couple of items of...so these are three pages that...got title in the page
...they laugh.
Also...I want to do with the page
...picked...page now so things...might want to do a synchronize pages with some of
...my out maybe I'm going to do list up and I want to synchronize a bunch of check boxes in one
night on the page so I'm going...the content for the page and then I'm going...update the content for the page.
So, we have a simple content property you can see on the page.
Which...scroll down to it...content url so that's kind of
the let me go and grab...content and just the same...as we created pages using
html content get back from one node is going to be html...that looks like?
It's going to pick one of these interesting pages when choose along with the capita on
it obviously polack.
And, then how...look at the html that we get back says we released very conveniently I'm going to use
...for visual studio...
And, to look at the html.
Aggregate.
you can see...this is actually fairly simple html think about gannon do views also atypical web
page html becomes by these days is pretty intimidating a lot of the time.
We tried very hard not to make this difficult...need to
...to be able to...go updated so,...some consequences...
What that means is this doesn't actually...brilliantly in a browsers
...html for page throw to into browser you have to see what's going on and you'll have a
...in the right position attaching the right position but...that pretty in the you know,
the fonts might be a little bit off if
you've got check boxes they're not going to show up because we just apply the data for check boxes not
...visual rendering that's a deliberate decision here to be able to say hey this html is
...process it updated and send it back into is not optimized for rendering?
And, see what we've got here is...body with attribute saying I'm going to enable
absolute positions and then I've got the first if...of text about caps.
Naturally...some shape specific...from...chrome and then and,
then whoops for scroll down to the bottom I've got my
absolutely position image and this time of course the image is not from the original source
...so we're not just a providing a web page re-direct and rendering
...other browser we've actually gone...image from the web...it in one...of
...so the url for the image it is from...resources...now bring
...because when you go and try and make a call on this you also going to need to
...authentication token when you make you get call on this to go and pull down the images I want to go and get
like aperture and, you would have to do that...normal browser session obviously you have
a url that was that was from the web originally...need any...so it's just something to remember
your coding against...you need to get...token in for every request okay so I've got now what about
...vietnam...my slides from imax is easy to explain from a slide.
Someone...
As I...free-form campus and, it's user model is not...programming database when you
sense...feed...can pretty much messed with anything you scented and,
that means the programming model for updating really needs to be about going and doing you
get the current content to the page accepting whatever the users done to it understanding
...the best you can and then changing that composting anatomically back to us
so the way you do that you...goal to get content...actual query parameter
include aidid's equals true what's going to do is...add an extra...to every element
this possible or...in the page so you've got something to immediately cool patch on.
Now there's a ideas and opposition...there for the moment but,
you use them in this patch language you can see the next lines
...you can patch almost saying url with the http patch...
This is very simple json language
...is to go make a change the page the target is one of those entities that we've just give you
an id back so in this case this is an...one element in my html with an
...what give it is and, then action can either be replace here
...replacing the...a woman capped although to go and append something on the
end of it or to go...something anywhere in the tree.
You can also parts the title.
And, you'll notice that when I'm replacingthe content I'm actually
starting some custom property data id equals case
so this is let me do is say hey this thing on page is something special that I'm going to come back to
...compact directly using kittens the id...not be good if
it still left remember don't rely on this stuff the user could've done anything to the page that could have
...deleting marketing heaven forbid.
So, again, you still even if you put those things in your page you still want to
...pull the...page back using include...I can do is really give you hints when you're
walking through the page to say up yes this is the first text underneath the
...naturally...I want to change that give you a way to map your way around the page
despite craziness of user changes that might have happened since last somebody...around.
And, then.
...thing you can do is just go and append to the core body of the page.
You can think about scenarios where you want to create some kind of log of ongoing data that's just coming
in filling in a one-page or daily status updates or something like that or even just a web blog.
So, let's go and see how that works.
So, we're...append here so it's choose a page to append two and I'm going to
...page...and cody both this ok so what I've done
here to be able to send that little patch language just created a simple dot net class.
My...action content to strings and then I'm just going to say realize that and send that over
...my request.
Such things.
So,...http client.
...my...is mile something like list of those patch plans you send a list of patch commands
and execute them sequentially in a batch I'm going to say...to the
...I'm going...and, given...what I know is the content to the page and
put some to much more importance in tongs.
Ok, and, then go run that.
Ok, apparently made horrible at it she wanted the...
Okay, well, I...to my super funny...consciously
...content...be grateful for and you can say I'm going to under success that I
can't think is really nothing to say about the patch having happened when I go...have a looking
woman hopefully that should start to show up.
So, is mine...then I'll just refresh that usually don't have
to refresher one-dimensional refresh model but sometimes they you know,
the run-up to the internet and then a batch operation can take a couple of seconds
...my new training content patched on to the page?
Okay, so.
That's all...basics.
That we've had for a while...also announcing today that we've got delete finally
...api so all of codec
...as you expect that's just the http delete up against the same page you arise.
...seen all of that so it wouldn't really be how often if...could do was take
...simple content text and images even through a great apertures and...out of one night we
...value on top of that.
So, we have a bunch of extra features where...go and take the things you...to...and do some more with them so,
for example, if you send...url?
Will go and grab that web page and, insert into a one that
text snapshots of it for you do...data...source attribute you can say here
so here ongoing grabbing...page of amazon-dot-com but, if you ask is to create
...image instead of dave we've just done that we're just...created an image in your one that page from
...because I dave and I said data random method equals extract
...smarter than just creating a...image will create the...we can't do
anything else but...going to do is try and extract some...from that web page instead
...something that's more useful to the user so for an...for amazon page,
for example, or any other product page will
goss great the actual interesting information the product details and just put
...is more ...more readable text on the page
...a typical example you...also begun partly the full-page tucked away
somewhere as well but, it's pretty nice to just be able to have the role product information on
the page when you captured it is what I...does?
The same for articles...the...url of a news article will give you a
...review of the news article rather...all the junk might be around...on the web page...vision
hosting and for recipe will gun instructor list of ingredients that's really the first thing you want to get...
And, the final one that we have some smarts around...going to dive into the in my mind
about is business cards song into...going to see a lot of the end of it?
...this new api for...for business we've changed our uri
...for anybody who's familiar with what we have in the consumer space over the last year to
...this me notes prefix tool value our eyes
...converge over three sixty five and
I consumer microsoft id logan's to give space to go and reach into
different uses accounts so, you'll see this now is as a preferred way of calling both I can see manned
...three sixty five api is and
then as we move forward will allow you to get replace that token of me with,
you know, bulb...can toes I dot com all...that microsoft-dot-com to go and reach into individual
people's accounts if you have missions and go...contribute to
...what with the shared one nuts and then we don't have this...today but we will have over the next couple of weeks
in beta a few to be able to work with one...to dom shared
sharepoint sites...gone reach into my organization and looking to the
...collection in the site with the appropriate...have a urimethod takes you arise from
a traditional...to allow you to go and what with those nobles so today that's
Will be in general availability sometime in the someone with all of this obviously the time we release that
we'll...
Will of...few little things we have a moment that are not the same as I...importance right now you
can't...notion of a default...book three sixty fivewhich means you can't just posto role
...just appear in...in a simple notebook so we'll have that...
We also have search moment you have...query that I showed, you know,
free text search will have...before...the moment the performance is not too hot on...three sixty
five we don't have a lot of indexing going on behind the scenes will have been running...atomic aegypt.
So, once we...gi next steps on this event to go and support the converged api
endpoint if you've seen any of those over three sixty five sessions where swishing to
...dot microsoft dot com to go and commish the...point across all of our api
...have the goodness of being able to walk from sharepoint server into its files
or into the one notenobles the store...will have that kind of support and then is the same
...groups?
So, far everything's really been kind of a bit theoretical is...essentially look at a real problem
pull it together so he's got a pocket full of business calls from people
that matter the convention, yeah, if you if you the rest of your obviously...to moment
...I'm certainly pick up an enormous amount as I go-round these things giving these talks
...the years.
...trying to...into outlook contacts have been pretty,
pretty good idea of but, my...contents contacts consequently built to the point
where there are thousands of them so that's pretty unwieldy omar devices
anonymously when I look download have this awful feeling of
...that because...some person I met for ten minutes in
...seven and I just don't have enough context to be able to remember
who they were so what I started to do is to stole my.
In one night.
And, although there's a nice field...
I never really felt motivated to use it but I just...started to just...to tiny little bit of
...scan of business code derivatives his business...from.
The guy comatose one-room screen.
Get from a guy comatose.
...somewhat with last year from...great...coming
...we put together matchup of one node and...any...a few years those couple of lines that I just typed in
around the just tell me that hey this is remembers the...the...with I'm showing you
enjoyed my memory enough to be able to work with it the one here from friend the
...colleague david mail who've been working with test some of our
api scaleability so this is just how I'm
...install these things are copied a couple over into my into my demo but for the session.
And, it's pretty nice.
I can go and click on you know, on davis email address and just go launch outlook.
And, we've even inserted the...object
...cult that I can just...click...contact if I do want to actually push somebody into my outlook
contact that I'm going to do business with a bit more frequently.
...great but it's a little bit of context switch...I'm still thinking...an email only talk
...email today if well okay I've got this flip over to one node to a quick search
chemical great search facilities and, go click on that and flip back into outlook can we do better than so,
let's look at the...we'd really like so somebody got a business...I can stale.
Go on one of the most of business...
As a prize in it for...
Does not motivate you to...pockets?
Now I know you
...of apprised now...you...now this gentleman the sorry there.
...also...api backpacked just for business code I hope it works.
All right so I've got...business god I'm going to pull...so I'm going to
...office lines now...this over to the element.
Ok, so, this is my iphone office
...not that were released across all mobile platforms.
Who...reflection?
phi that up and it's essentially a virtual scanner.
Some scum...
Take a...
Sticky down...business...
Health...put inside...so roma the document so you can say what
...done that is gone and,...the aspect ratio the really rubbish
...that I...going to remove any reflections are just really nice image processing to give you the best possible image
you can...that image so I'm just...say done.
And, I'm going to send across the one that nicely done how to build of office
...on my find sends directly to offer three sixty five so I'm going to change a little bit here and...it to my consumer
...just copyrighted across some gunnison across.
And, you see that transferring and I'll go
and pull my account up over...the machine...that's doing its thing okay.
So, switch into my consumer camps...
There we go those there it is appearing so I'm just going to take a copy of
...and move into morpheus three...
And,...in...all right so...on...
So, you can see what this is the content
...business...and it's going to do not nice extraction and...
ok so...going to look at the code would've worked so that under the covers.
So, we can look...create pages and create page with business code.
And, go and debug that so what I'm going to do now is if I want to send that kind of thing for business
...virtually got the image locally
must gunner application as a bitmap...that kind of data across the
want api and do that in a single round-trip we actually just...in a multiple
...message super easy to do in most languages to go and just...envelope around
it to send a binary stream into send the html consumes in the same packet just look how that works?
Take a look at the html...
You can see what I'm doing here is inserting a dave my html with my data
...method because...is going to fire off
...business called extraction and this on semi data into
...I've got this funny little name...the one obviously is muttering is my print
...where I'm going to put in the name of my multiple
...contains the image and then name colon is a little url protocol...we've got in the
...api this as a if you go to multiple message and name
...pick out the data from the named part in the multiple messages all parts
...message have a unique name?
So, that's going to use can
...that data and...research referee data into fullback which is going to say.
If we were unable for some reason to extract anything from this what would you like
...today would you like...just put the image or would you like...do nothing nachos
...of chosen...pretty good bet to say
known than actually go and you can see the live directly put in the images well
so always be the image of the business college and then option little-bitty extracted component
...the top so always have both and,
I'll fullback essentially to just having the image okay so?
I'm going to go and read a business garden out I'm not good enough camron this laptop to have done the
to have actually done the photo take on a laptop so I'm actually just...
Retreating...business...that odf of created you can see this not super-high resolutely to
be perfect but it's still better than itemized my camera my laptop unloading that
...this...code and...creating a message
...posting in this case to hard coded...obviously you'd go and choose...section in your application
code business cards and go and find the idea of that by the api we let the
...pick where they wanted to put it as you saw in the picker in office
...just hard coded xml so making http request message with multiple the
content.
Super simple as...just a few lines of code...content from my html and
then the binary content with my image part so corona.
We get out of created it and once again going copy
...one-a url.
And, actually approached easy to load and
...look nunn-lugar just...so there's my has to...with my nasty
...business called super easy to go...kind of thing and build...applications like office...
...what do I actually want to do without solve the problem well.
I've got here that I'm going to...and show you
is imagine for outlook so I had that experience of going into one
...and clicking only email address not...a contact switch...much rather just access this data is those
...of secondary contact book inside outlook.
Hopefully that's fide up.
Crime started...
So, I just created this using the with it so, there is going to
...to solution project visual studio will come back and look about later.
...pfizer parallel just so you get a sense of where...is...again with this I
...to go...as an...into outlook to work in the compose.
Screen for creating...really that's where the time are most wanting to go and, pick
...to...from my pseudo address book in...in one that if I can say.
...my outspoken shows up and then I'm going to nice out one night for
...choose that.
...wife a little bit and go and pull out all of those business...with a bit of look.
So, there again and as well.
So, I'm just guns and...email very trivially even though that's not store anywhere
...outlook until if I want to...a...well that's an easy thing to do
ok so has...built...just before I show you that closely...a great thing about
this...an added for outlook of...is this
...all versions of outlook so here's a desktop version arrogance apps for
office in their could equally be the...go to the versions...supporting the obviously
...start that and exactly the same thing happens in the desktop version running
exactly the same code from the same server america has...choose and...
And, then we...samoa ability it's kind of look at...time.
So, I just use the...here.
So, if I use...start this up I'm going to new project and then just choose office and
choose apps for office and that was...trust me we chops I wanted to run it
...criterias outlook I'd get a project looks like this.
With a couple solution...looks like this.
...couple of projects so just one very trivial project this essentially got a
...file just describes how my applications can run inside office where he lives on the server.
Where it's which web pages should startand,
how it should how should run so in should within the...the reformed...I...to within the compose
...for e-mail messages when I do on when you start this home page inside my
...which is the second...so the web out the which would just create
...completely static web page which great, you know, it's a good way to get started but obviously mostly
that one static html server these things you want something dynamic...from the server
...converting modernization...got to...
...what you see down here is
...usual nbc stuff so I've got a couple of controller's...my home controller which matches
the page which I'm starting which is going to do some very simple logic to say hey you already have a
cookie that sign dating to the service if...done it then I'm going to re-direct
...across to the of endpoint...reader...the...point that's going
to do is...magic and, then bounced back through the lthree
direct mechanism to another...got such open...that's actually going to go and do
a token exchange and then...that into a cookie that I can use in my front and web page and
then bouncing back yet again to my home control which this time when I run it is going to say yes,
I have...cookie so I better show the view
...view these should expect the list so let's see how that works?
So,...down here is a super simple page can really get more trivial that just says hey there's an
empty...called sections on that text of...contents and then that sessions
just gets...dynamically bomb-making goals from the client-side to the api of course...could this is html
...could gone just made all articles on the server perfectly reasonable thing to do what I want to show you
that we can run this code both you...the author from the server-side I'm going to the api
...in the client-side so you can do very dynamic ajax base thing that's the way I'm going to coded and
that we support the codes and,...necessary to be able to do that from
our api so all of the code lives in this...js file.
Mine javascript is very rusty so a big thanks to guinier almighty...help me a
...with this because I really...struggle to code itself otherwise any mistakes and
...things...entirely mine though...his so,
I'm going to run the page up I'm going to...call to the service just all things up and get some rule data...I'm
going to make here is to get to the notes sections and...I'm going to get all of the sections.
I'm going to get their id in the in...they couldn't...database...pick particular
...somewhat...bj on packets back across the water...the idea name or
...aid and then I'm going to use that expand function we described earlier and pull down the pages in
the sections again I'm going to ask for the title of the page in the id I'm going to say you
also and get the content url field...content to the web page because they actually did
an indiscriminate call here I'm getting all of the pages in my notebook I'm actually no...business
...point later in the a will have search api that let you actually go and say hey I'd like
all the pages they've got business cards in all of the pages with products and...brute force approach.
So, having pulled those down...call load page content without data and one of got
...but down because I've done the expand is an st structure where I've got a list of sections and
...of pages so I've just got a nasty for located to move
...and for each of those pages I'm going to get need to pull the content and say
...to business cold inside...now so I'm going to q a bunch of
...here just by putting them on to a list to the pages and...
and the page them board passing the idea that I go back from the structure...the content of the end of
...content property having...those...a q I'm just going to let the
browser will through as fast as it can asynchronous recalling those and,
taking the results of those goals which we might terms of html.
And, sticking those mapped into
...so I'm going to make those...here and not the main.
And, then I get the array back is going to be
...of html...I can walk across driven from the asynchronous...
Some...through that html I'm going to very like...showing into...just to go
...a finally that dave...going to...dave that's on
the page holding the business called if there is one and, if there is I would like to look for
the object tag so the object eigen html is html as
...attachments time...the same way we do on page attachments and one so I've got obviously have called
...and...say hey...any...the any object tags
...finally one's whose name contains...cf...and obviously...anyway,
it's just a simple way to say hey give me the ones that actually got something I can use a content for outlook.
And, if I've got any of those...if this is a new section go and create some a
ui for the section with the dave in outlook in the pain and then for
each the entry goin' create dave for the actual page
...business...use the name of the business...the name of the pages...not least in the
...as one final thing I need to do...page I didn't want to go and pulled
...business called I knew was there I've got the object tag but that's not the database if I
...to...for all of them just because spending so, I thought I do the pool when you...click on the
...enough to be able to do that so I just set up again so when I into a click that I'm going to do
one more ajax cool I'm going to pass in the resource url in the tokens
or if you remember we said that when you need to the second recall again get...in this case a business
...pcs file...the token
...to make electrical...just pick it up automatically and
...the data attribute on the object...standard html data attribute...says hey
is the stream which actually backs the attachment and, then pulling down the token from the computer
...so that's my click handler
...thing...actually do something with the data?
So, when it gets...the lasting...is the as...cf
positive obviously if...actually just a...a new separated file with name
cologne value structures in the...out for the first name
and email address very simply not json I'm passing that
...the ads recipients and this is where I'm going to call some of the outlook javascript
object model very trivial piece about to just going to say ...the message to compose I want to
...to the to failed and send the address that I've created so really,
really simple code to get really quite a rich experience it outlook?
You can think of the... relatively professional integration.
So, we see that we
saw a rich mobile application but using incredibly simple code
get myspace value from the service that we've provided gung...not business...extraction.
Equally...the same products articles and then and
...office...to reach the huge number of hundreds of millions of users.
And, thinking of this as a digital memory...
We haven't had to go...all of us contacts into our transactional contact stole this
is really great way that we think one note can be used...say hey I've got all
of this stuff that's in some intermediate state is either an early form for
...a project...if you people working on isn't quite finish it or...contact
that's not really ready to be my main contacts just one might need some point...want to gun
rights and extra context around that so this...structured data and completely
lose unstructured data which one...really...but then I want to
gung push that into a productivity experience on-the-fly...surface dynamically.
So,...rightnow of http code creating things...people large code like
...equally love people refer to use and sdk...embassy most of http
givens out so we're announcing today are first...case files android.
So, next time you see coding...a lot this I'll probably do one using...and http stuff
therejust grab...get...with the rest of the office st case but,
the moment value...consumer endpoint she's the...production as opposed
...we'll...without...support satan so...tanaka general availability
...android and I also a...portable and probably a bunch of other libraries as time goes by
...on get hope there's just a little sample...of the the aisles code.
...we're going with all this seems pretty great usage.
And, scenarios to use with what we currently got the...a lot more to come
...a very strongly from my uses the reacting to changes in one that is a
key scenario synchronization between data...apps and data
...one is very popular thing to want to kind of...you have to go and poll against service
...you polling answer service we can cope with it but obviously it's pretty unpleasant thing to
...interviews will have web...to allow you to just go and register change notifications obviously going to be the
...case as I said...data samples to use those st case?
Income one notice a huge part of our rich content story and today business support for to api
as...going to want to add that so
you can bring the reaching based features into your own applications.
Copy notebooks make it mine it's really interesting start to use one night as
a lightweight publishing...say hey...a public one note with some more some content
...with us in the education space all advertising or
...running...of some sort of promotion on the web
and you've got some content you want people to take...their...stories around say on
...new products and I want to get people to write a
daria...usage of it and send it back to me on a competition my people...to
...short story about something and I've got a story template I want to put out there and have people submit
those back really compelling scenario that's been really difficult to achieve so fileso, having
...to allow you to go and copy network into customers account into uses count?
Also just...directly the one I climb so when I come to a
...notebook they can say hey make copy of this mine
saloon those scenarios up we've also heard from me that it's the moment to
hog to actually get recognition so we've...of applications but, you know,
people have actually got to go to that not everybody does all the time so we people one better ways to
surface applications and to bring...use communities...together so
...to support those and finally in terms of things that...currently go engineers working...
Is...ability to go embed one...your own applications so people
of asses again and again to say hey this data integrations fine but we have some ui integration can
I just go and plop one notice piece of note-taking goodness in the middle of my app and later in the will have
that ability fpga sky
frame a one-page input inside your application super quickly super easily and,
get all of a value in just a couple of lines of code so
this robot going out after a couple of weeks now on the web truncated public...that we pretty open on the
...a lot of these things came from ideas that
...heavily voted on...voice a lot of things were already done things that we've completed on use
...we really do take it seriously it's something that ...know
we really focus our planning process so, please go...contributes on there?
So, if you only use the officer sixty-five api obviously you can any...three
sixty five account easiest way to get that is the new over three sixty five developer program
...dev office dot com deaf program typically sign up for free develop a subscription
...also the extra goodness as well
tools training newsletters to see what's coming out find out when we go ga that kind of thing.
...to action view.
First thing is consumer api...in...to go actually ship applicants
...can do that right now go home build apps using all of that reach that I've shown
you all of it works as well as...consumer as well as...three sixty-five with exactly the same and
...now that converged...code who were pretty much and altered me
go ga against the against the...sixty-five...you can...the consumer ones today.
Start plainly over three sixty-five stuff tell us whether any gaps
...as...throughout...preview cycle ...migration
...consumer apps that you've already got to use the me...notes...
Particular think about your line-of-business applications and how you can integrate those great source
for data people...also some notes all things they want to compose you can imagine
...performance reviews rather than just in some nasty...web tool go and do those in want to be able
to upload those ...go and push reports into and...as a way to go in and distribute
your organizational data to folks?
Tells what you need as...said unusable...really taken seriously.
...just focus on twitter.
The team rule on the product team it's not just marketing folks so,
resource...is that one I don't call
...everything I've talked about today and, when I...handle really do want you to engage with is on...
Please...time if you like caps to evaluate this section.
The...people out there I'd really rather didn't okay
...taken time...with me until the end here...of the politic.